Guide to the J. DuPratt White papers, 1915-1939.
White, J. DuPratt papers, 1915-1939.
- Buildings and Grounds
  - Correspondence re C.U. Medical College, Oct. 1920-June 1921 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Information on Pension Plans, 1926-1928 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence re C.U. Medical College, June 1927-Dec. 1927 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence re C.U. Medical College, June 1928-Dec. 1929 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence re C.U. Medical College, Jan. 1930-Dec. 1931 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - William H. Sage Memorial Pension Fund Endowment, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Sale of Old Medical Buildings Correspondence, Nov. 1931, Jan. 1932-June 1932 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Law School Correspondence, July 1932-Sept. 1932 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence re Sale of Old Medical Buildings, Aug. 1932 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence re Sale of Old Medical Buildings Sale to N.Y. University closed Sept. 25, 1932, Sept. 1932 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence re Sale of Old Medical Buildings, Oct. 1932 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Law School Correspondence, Oct. 1932-Nov. 1932 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence re C.U. Medical College, Jan. 1932-Apr. 1933 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Law School Correspondence, Jan. 1933-Oct. 1933 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence re C.U. Medical College, May 1933-Apr. 1934 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Law School Correspondence, Mar. 1934-Dec. 1934 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence re C.U. Medical College, June 1934-Dec. 1935 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Law School Correspondence, Jan. 1935-Nov. 1935 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Law School Correspondence, Jan. 1936-Oct. 1936 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Law School Correspondence, Nov. 1936-Dec. 1936 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Law School Correspondence, Jan. 1937-Apr. 1937 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - C.U. Group Insurance Information, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Law School Correspondence, May 1937-Dec. 1937 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - C.U. Pension Plans, 1932, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Law School Correspondence, Jan. 1938-July 1939 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Clippings re Merger of N.Y. Hospital and Cornell Medical Center, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Documents re Sale of Medical Buildings in New York City, 1932, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Documents re Sale of Medical Buildings in New York City, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Historical Sketch of C.U. Medical College; By-Laws and Ordinances; Welcoming Address by William Ladd, M.D., 1927-1936 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Memo re Medical College Securities received from the Estate of Payne Whitney, May 21, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence re C.U. Medical College, Feb. 1935-Dec. 1935 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence re C.U. Medical College, Jan. 1936-Jan. 1937 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Agreement for District Health and Training Center in NYC in Conjunction with NY Hospital - Cornell Medical College, 1935, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence re C.U. Medical College, Jan. 1937-May 1939 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence re C.U. Medical College, Jan. 1938-Dec. 1938 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence re C.U. Medical College, Jan. 1939 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Agreements, Costs, and Allotments, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Fundraising for C.U. War Memorial. Brochures and Pamphlets, 1926-1927 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - War Memorial I, July 22, 1926-Jan. 1, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - War Memorial II, July 22, 1926-Jan. 1, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - War Memorial I, Jan. 1, 1928-July 1, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - War Memorial II, Jan. 1, 1928-July 1, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - War Memorial I, July 1, 1928-July 1, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - War Memorial II, July 1, 1928-July 1, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - War Memorial I, July 1, 1929-July 1, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - War Memorial II, July 1, 1929-July 1, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - File 6, Part IB - Group Insurance and Pensions Committee, Apr. 21, 1931-June 23, 1931 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Group Insurance and Pensions Committee, July 1, 1931-Jan. 1, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Group Insurance and Pensions Committee, July 1, 1931-Jan. 1, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Group Insurance and Pensions Committee, Jan. 1, 1935-Mar. 2, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Group Insurance and Pensions Committee, Jan. 1, 1935-Mar. 2, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - War Memorial, July 1, 1930-Mar. 13, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - War Memorial, July 1, 1930-Mar. 13, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - File 6, Part IA - Group Insurance and Pensions Committee, Apr. 8, 1922-Apr. 20, 1931 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - File 6, Part IA - Group Insurance and Pensions Committee, Apr. 8, 1922-Apr. 20, 1931 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Honor Roll of Cornellians who Fell in World War I (264 names), No date (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Room Memorials Donated in Honor of Those Who Fell in World War I, No date (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report of the Professor of Military Science and Tactics at Cornell University, 1931-1932 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Military Training, May 25, 1931-Dec. 10, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Military Training, May 25, 1931-Dec. 10, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - War Memorial Plans and Drawings [RESTRICTED], 1927-1929 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Pamphlets, Memos, and Reports re Military Training at C.U., 1926-1933 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Selection of New President, June-Dec. 1935 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Selection of New President, Jan. -Feb. 1936 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Selection of New President, Mar. -April 1936 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Selection of New President, May-June 1936 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - 1-D (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - 1-E (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Portrait of Pres. Farrand for Law School, Nov. -June 1936 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - 3-A McMullen Scholarships, April-July 1923 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - 3-A McMullen Scholarships, June-Dec. 1924 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - 3-A McMullen Scholarships, Jan.-Nov. 1925 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - 3-A McMullen Scholarships, Mar. 1926-Dec. 1927 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - 3-A McMullen Scholarships, Jan. 1928-Dec. 1929 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - 3-A McMullen Scholarships, Jan.-Oct. 1930 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - 3-B McMullen Scholarships, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - 3-B McMullen Scholarships, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - 3-B McMullen Scholarships, 1933 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - 3-B McMullen Scholarships, 1934-1935 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - 3-C McMullen Scholarships, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - 3-C McMullen Scholarships, Jan.-Aug. 1937 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - 3-C McMullen Scholarships, Sept.-Dec. 1937 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - 3-C McMullen Scholarships, 1938-1939 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - File 4-C Miscellaneous, 1916-1939 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - File 4-C Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - File 4-C Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - File 4 Statutes of Cornell University, 1937-1939 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - 4-D University Seal, 1937-1938 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Tuition and Loan Notes and Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Tuition and Loan Notes and Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Tuition and Loan Notes and Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - 6-1 Architectural Advisory Board, 1927 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - 6-2 Baker Lab, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - 6-3 Baker Lab - leaking, 1929 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - 6-5 Board of Trustees, 1926-1930 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - 6-6 Boldt Tower and Memorial, 1929-0930 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - 6-7 Buildings, 1926-1929 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - 6-8 Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1927-1930 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - 6-9 Campus, 1926-1928 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - 6-10 Committees Meetings, 1928-1930 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - 6-11 Electrical Contract, 1926-1928 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - 6-12 Engineering Bldgs., 1928 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - 6-14 Fire Hazard, 1928 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - 6-15 Fraternity Housing, 1927-1929 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - 6-19 Gifts, 1926-1929 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - 6-20 Home EC. building, 1929 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - 6-21 Kuichling, Mrs. Sarah L., 1919-1920 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - File I Committee Reports, etc., Misc., 1935-1936 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - File I Committee Reports, etc., Misc., 1935 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - File 1D Selection of Pres. Day, Edmund Ezra (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - File 1D Goodrich, Herbert F. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - File 1D Bayne-Jones, Stanhope (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - File 1D Fox, Dixon Ryan (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - File 1D Mann, Albert Russell (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - File 1D Mc Conaughy, James Lukens (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - File 1D Robinson, Edgar Eugene (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - File 1D Tate, John Torrence (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - File 1D Committee of Selection of Pres. - Preliminary List (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - File 1D Jessup, Phi ip Caryl (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - File 1D Shepardson, Whitney Hart (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - File 1D Adams, James Pickwell; Aydelotte, Frank (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - File 1D Bigelow, Karl W.; Baxter, James Phinney; Bressler, Raymond George; Bush, Vannevar (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - File 1D Chase, Henry Woodburn; Clothier, Robert Clarkson; Compton, Karl Taylor (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - File 1D Dickinson, John (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - File 1D Dykstra, Clarence Addison (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - File 1D Furness, Edgar Stephenson (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - File 1D Gaines, Francis Pendleton; Garrison, Lloyd Kirkham; Graham, Frank Porter; Gregg, Alan (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - File 1D Hanford, Alfred Chester; Hayden, Joseph Ralston; Hetzel, Ralph Dorn (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - File 1D Johnson, Sveinbjorn; King, Stanley (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - File 1D Merritt, Benjamin Dean; Murdock, Kenneth Ballard; Myers, William Irving; Middlebush, Fred. A.,- Moore, Henry T. (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - File 1D Rainey, Homer Price,- Rogers, James Grafton,-Ruml, Beardsley; Russell, William Fletcher; Ruthven, Alexander Grant (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - File 1D Scammon, Richard Everingham; Smith, Thomas Vernon; Sproul, Robert Gordon (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - File 1D Urey, Harold Clayton; Willey, Malcolm MacDonald; Wittke, Carl Frederick (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Wriston, Henry Merritt (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Committee on Selection of New President, 1936-1937 (Box 16, Folder 28-31)
  - 2B Lefevre Will, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - 24 Library, Addition to, 1928 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Maps, 1929 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - 26 McMullen Estate, 1926-1929 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - 27 Men's Dormitories, 1927-1929 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - 28 Pension, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - 29 Personal Corres. with Bostwick, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - 30 Phi Gamma Delta, 1926-1929 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - 31 Plant Industry Building, 1927-1928 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - 32 Quill and Dagger [RESTRICTED], 1927-1928 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - 33 Radio Station, 1927 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - 34 Reports - Emer. Notes - G.D.Haupin, 1935-1939 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - 35 Reports on Financial Transactions, 1929-1930 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - 36 Roads, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - 37 Scorpion, 1926-1927 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - 38 Securities, Care of, 1927-1928 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - 39 Service Building, 1927-1929 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - 40 Sharp Patent, 1928 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - 41 Stone, 1926-1929 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - 42 Taylor Hall, Myron, 1928-1930 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - 43 Tower Road, 1927 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - 44 Veterinary College, 1929 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - 45 War Memorial, 1927-1929 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - 46 Water Supply, 1926-1928 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - 47 White Fund, J. DuP., 1927-1929 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - White, J. DuPratt, 1939-1940 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - 48 Women's Dormitories, 1926-1928 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - 16 16 General, 1926-1929 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - 17 General, 1929-1930 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - 18 General - Education Board, Soc. NY Hospital, 1928 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - 13 Finance Committee, 1926-1929 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - 14 Fire Hazard, 1928 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - 15 Fraternity Housing, 1927-1929 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - 19 Gifts, 1926-1929 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - 20 Home EC. Building, 1929 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - 21 Kuichling, Mrs. Sarah L., 1919-1920 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - 22 Law School, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Gift, Endowments, Stocks and Bonds re C.U., 1918-1920; 1926-1929 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - New Home Economics Building, 1929 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - C.U. Committee on Campus Fraternities, 1927-1929 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Campus Fire Hazard Situations, 1928 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Investments, Securities, Stock Market Conditions, 1926-1929 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - General Education Board - New York Hospital, 1927-1928 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - General University Buisness - State Colleges, Insurance, Building Maitenance, 1927-1929 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Four Pamphlets: C.U. Group Insurance; History of Glenn Frank - Prospective Republican Presidential Candidate for 1936; The System of "Stealing" Party Nominations; Students against War, 1935 (Box 17, Folder 8)